

## Contact

muradovtahir01@gmail.com Baku city, Ahmadli district, M.Hadi street

+994-55-278-43-44

https://github.com/TahirMuradov

https://www.linkedin.com/in/tahirmuradov-94bb98271/

## Skills

- HtmlCss (SCSS,SASS)
- Bootstrap,TailwindCSS, MaterialUI
- JavaScript (TypeScript)
- ReactJS,NextJs
- GIT, GITHUB
- C# Asp.Net Core
- Entity Framework
- Mvc
- N-Tier Architecture
- MsSql
- Oop
- REST API (swaggerUI)

# **Experience**

<u>WebConsole Studio</u> Intern Software Developer 03.2024-04.2024

<u>Compar Academy</u> Mentor Full-Stack Developer (C#) 012.2023-03.2024

# Language

- Turkish
- English
- Russian

# **Tahir Muradov**

# .NET DEVELOPER

## **About**

In 2018, I graduated from secondary school and was admitted to the Computer Science program at Azerbaijan Technical University. In 2022, I pursued further education by enrolling in the Master's program in Computer Engineering at the same university.

Additionally, I completed a Full-Stack Web Development program at Compar Academy, where I developed strong programming and problem-solving skills. After graduating from the academy, I worked as a C# backend developer intern at WebConsole Studio, further enhancing my technical expertise and understanding of software development processes.

# **Projects**

**Shoes Ecommerce** https://shoes-next-js.vercel.app/ NextJs 14,Next-Intl,NextAuth,TypeScript,Tailwindcss,MaterialUI development continues.

#### **ShoesApi**

(API, N-Tier architecture, supported multi language validate error messages with Fluent Validation , JWTToken)

#### <u>zmt.az</u>

WebConsole Studio

(MVC, N-Tier architecture, A web application with admin panel)

#### Karl Fashion (MVC)

(MVC, N-Tier architecture,add to cart , e-order creator(pdf) ,Fluent Validation, IdentityToken,multi-language support))

#### Karl Fashion(API)

(API, N-Tier architecture, ,Fluent Validation, JWT Token)

#### <u>AzTU-Event (Electronic Event Management System)</u>

(MVC, N-Tier architecture, Multiple language support error messages, MVC, N-Tier architecture, Fluent Validation, IdentityToken, multi-language support)

## Education

#### (2018-2022) Bachelor's degree

Azerbaijan Technical University
Computer science

### (2022-2024) Master's degree

Azerbaijan Technical University
Computer Engineering

## (2022-2023) Full Stack Web Development

Compar Academy